<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_NonViolence</defName>
		<label>vow of nonviolence</label>
		<description>We are committed to bringing about a world of peace, harmony, laughter, and love. We take this vow to be nonviolent in our thoughts, our speech, and our actions.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733&gt;This is a very challenging meme, as ALL colonists of this ideoligion will be incapable of combat, and can only defend themselves in three ways: traps, turrets, and having a multi-ideo colony with some "defenders" who don't share the same values.&lt;/color&gt;\n\nOskar quote: "please no xd this is actually game breaking".</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_NonViolence</iconPath>
		<groupDef>Misc</groupDef>
		<exclusionTags>
			<li>VME_TooViolent</li>
			<li>VME_PacifistsNotViolentConverters</li>
			<li>VME_TooHonourable</li>
			<li>VME_NotRaiders</li>
			<li>VME_NoCannibalsAndNonviolenceVow</li>
			<li>VME_NonViolenceVoteVsRancher</li>
			<li>VME_SadistVsNonviolence</li>
		</exclusionTags>
		<impact>3</impact>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->nonviolent</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->peace-loving</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->harmonious</li>
				<li>memeLeaderNoun->conscientious objector</li>
				<li>memeMoralist->passive resister</li>
				<li>memeConcept->nonviolence</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_NonViolence)        ->[deity0_name] made all of [deity0_possessive] followers swear a solemn vow of nonviolence.</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_NonViolence)  ->Speaking to the believers, [deity0_name] said: "Violence is the ultimate sin. It is preferable to be slaughtered than to raise a hand against other human being".</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_NonViolence)           ->[place_summary] [place_name] was always fraught with conflict. The [memberNamePlural] were besieged constantly by terrible warmongers, and this deeply saddened [deity0_name].</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_NonViolence)        ->[deity0_name] witnessed the contant assaults of a terrible [foeLeader], a war leader, and how [foeLeader_pronoun] was always planning some sort of violence.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_NonViolence)     ->[deity0_name], tired of all the violence, infused the [foeLeader] with [deity0_pronoun] love, and [foeLeader_pronoun] immediately had a change of heart. From that point on, the [foeLeader] took [foeLeader_possessive] new name as the [deity0_name]'s speaker: [founderName] the Nonviolent.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_NonViolence)         ->[founderName] made us all understand that love is the only way forward, and we all swore a solemn vow of nonviolence.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_NonViolence)           ->[founderName] was a monk. [founder_pronoun] spent decades of [founder_possessive] life teaching that a world of peace, harmony, laughter, and love can only be created by outright rejecting all violence, in all its forms.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_NonViolence)    ->[founderName] understood better than anyone else that violence is a poison to the soul, and that we must refuse to retaliate in the face of provocation and violence.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_NonViolence)         ->The ancient sages of Earth were absolutely right. They teach us that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_NonViolence)              ->a world of peace, harmony, laughter, and love can only be created by outright rejecting all violence, in all its forms</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_NonViolence) ->We must refuse to retaliate in the face of provocation and violence.</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_NonViolence)    ->Archotechs are pure minds, and they didn't get to their state by imposing their will upon others.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_NonViolence)     ->Violence is inherently abhorrent to advanced minds, the last resort of the weak of spirit.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_NonViolence) ->[inTheEnd], only those who refuse to retaliate in the face of provocation and violence will be ready to transcend.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_NonViolence)    ->The spirits teach us that a world of peace, harmony, laughter, and love can only be created by outright rejecting all violence, in all its forms.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_NonViolence)     ->Feeding the spirit of violence is senseless and wasteful, for violence is the ultimate sin.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_NonViolence) ->[itIsSaid] only those who refuse to retaliate in the face of provocation and violence will be ready to commune with the spirits.</li>
					<!-- serketist -->
					<li>serketistProphecy(tag=meme_NonViolence)->[itIsSaid] we will understand that a hive of peace, harmony, laughter, and love can only be created by outright rejecting all violence, in all its forms.</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_NonViolence)->Violence is just sustenance for these ancient entities, for they feed on terror. We must refuse to retaliate in the face of their provocation and violence.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_NonViolence)->Occult knowledge can't enter a mind occupied by violence and strife. Violence is a poison to the soul, and we must refuse to retaliate in the face of provocation and violence.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_NonViolence)->However, we are not killers. If we become murderers, how are we any better than this cursed Universe? We will be witnesses to the coming Apocalypse, but we won't be bearers of the weapons that bring its justice.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_NonViolence)->We are writing to remind you that the mandatory online anger management seminar has been rescheduled to this next Tuesday. Remember, people, in this company we are committed to bringing about a world of peace, harmony, laughter, and love!</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>VME_Raiding_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>Slavery_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Violence_Abhorrent_Strict</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>Execution_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>VME_MeatEating_Abhorrent_Strict</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AnimalSlaughter_Prohibited</li>
				<li>AnimalSlaughter_Horrible</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>KillingInnocentAnimals_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>TreeCutting_Disapproved</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Nonviolence</ideoName>
				<theme>nonviolence</theme>
				<adjective>nonviolent</adjective>
				<member>pacifist</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
		<addDesignators>
			<li>AM_TrapBlunt</li>
		</addDesignators>
		<modExtensions>
			<li Class="VanillaMemesExpanded.ExtendedMemeProperties">
				<forcedTrait>AM_Ahimsa</forcedTrait>
			</li>
		</modExtensions>
	</MemeDef>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_Artist</defName>
		<label>artist</label>
		<description>Art is unquestionably one of the purest and highest elements in human happiness. It trains the mind through the eye, and the eye through the mind. As the sun colours flowers, so does art colour life.</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_Artist</iconPath>
		<groupDef>Misc</groupDef>
		<impact>2</impact>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->artistic</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->creative</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->imaginative</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->expressive</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->aesthetic</li>
				<li>memeLeaderNoun->sculptor</li>
				<li>memeMoralist->art critic</li>
				<li>memeConcept->art</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_Artist)        ->[deity0_name] taught all of [deity0_possessive] followers to paint, write and sculpt, for all those activities were sacred to [deity0_objective].</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_Artist)  ->Speaking to [deity0_possessive] believers, [deity0_name] said: "Every child is an artist. The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up".</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_Artist)           ->[place_summary] [place_name] was a place renowned for its collections of fine art dedicated to [deity0_name].</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_Artist)        ->A greedy [foeLeader], wanting to increase [foeLeader_possessive] already obscene riches, wanted to sell all the art and get rid of it.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_Artist)     ->[deity0_name] inspired our founder, [founderName], with incredible creativity, and a work of art of such wondrous quality was created that the [foeLeader] broke into tears, moved by its beauty.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_Artist)         ->[founderName] made us all understand that art enables us to find ourselves and lose ourselves at the same time.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_Artist)           ->[founderName] was a painter, often compared to the great artists of old Earth. [founder_pronoun] spent decades perfecting [founder_possessive] style, and [founder_pronoun] was considered a true master.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_Artist)    ->[founderName] understood better than anyone else that art is not what you see, but what you make others see.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_Artist)         ->You need only to study the ancient history of art to understand that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_Artist)              ->you don't make mistakes, just happy little accidents</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_Artist) ->Art is not what you see, but what you make others see.</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_Artist)    ->Archotechs are pure creativity. Pristine minds with an infinite capacity for imagination.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_Artist)     ->There is nothing the archotechs despise more than a person who doesn't create new things.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_Artist) ->[inTheEnd], only those who have embraced their creative side will be ready to transcend.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_Artist)    ->The spirit of creativity is one of the strongest, for it governs everything that involves human imagination.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_Artist)     ->The act of creating new things is sacred to the spirits.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_Artist) ->[itIsSaid] only those who have embraced their creative side will be ready to commune with the spirits.</li>
					<!-- serketist -->
					<li>serketistProphecy(tag=meme_Artist)->[itIsSaid] we will create intricate designs representing the myriad variations of our beloved insects.</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_Artist)->Only a real artist knows the actual anatomy of the terrible or the physiology of fear - the exact sort of lines and proportions that connect up with latent instincts or hereditary memories of fright, and the proper colour contrasts and lighting effects to stir the dormant sense of strangeness.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_Artist)->Who knows what secret patterns hide behind these arcane secrets? We will create wondrous works of art and study them to discover what lays beyond.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_Artist)->Every act of creation is first of all an act of destruction.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_Artist)->Could you *please* look again into the problems the art department has with their computers? I think they have installed something they shouldn't...</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>AM_ArtProductionSpeed_Increased</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Art_Desired</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_ArtQuality_Expected</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>VME_AutomationEfficiency_Decreased</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Art</ideoName>
				<theme>art</theme>
				<adjective>artistic</adjective>
				<member>artist</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
	</MemeDef>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_Madness</defName>
		<label>madness</label>
		<description>A setback of the heart is often one floor above you, onomatopoeia as a weapon of mental destruction. Are the roosters fighting?! I hope not! All turtles are stupid.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733&gt;*ahem* The non-crazy part... This meme is based around getting huge bonuses after mental breaks... At the expense of having mental breaks quite often. Powerful... if you can get around the crazed shenanigans.&lt;/color&gt;</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_Madness</iconPath>
		<groupDef>Misc</groupDef>
		<impact>2</impact>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->insane</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->mad</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->crazy</li>
				<li>memeLeaderNoun->madman</li>
				<li>memeMoralist->maniac</li>
				<li>memeMoralist->lunatic</li>
				<li>memeConcept->madness</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_Madness)        ->[deity0_name] faced [deity0_possessive] followers and turned their minds inside out.</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_Madness)  ->Speaking to [deity0_possessive] believers, [deity0_name] said: "My children, you must face the dirty truth about knitting". Which didn't apply to the current situation at all, but that's why [deity0_pronoun] is the deity of Madness.</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_Madness)           ->[place_summary] [place_name] was a place where madness reigned, for the glory of [deity0_name].</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_Madness)        ->A conniving [foeLeader], wanting to impose [foeLeader_possessive] will on [deity0_name]'s followers, tried to attack with the help of a powerful army.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_Madness)     ->[deity0_name] inspired our founder, [founderName], with complete insanity, and [founder_pronoun] assaulted the huge army on [founder_possessive] own. Naked.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_Madness)         ->In a stroke of mad luck, [founderName] struck the [foeLeader] on the head with a throwing rock, and the rest of the army couldn't help but stare in awe as a single crazed loony had singlehandedly killed their leader. Then of course they tore [founderName] to pieces.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_Madness)           ->[founderName] was a very wise person. [founder_pronoun] had the gift of being able to paint songs and smell paintings on Tuesdays. [founder_pronoun] loved wildcrafted limberger paste topped with room temperature scallop tea. Without a hint of cinnamon, that would be madness.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_Madness)    ->[founderName] always repeated the same sentence over and over again. And again. And again: no man on the Rim has no belly-button, it proves every believer on the Rim a liar.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_Madness)         ->Let me tell you: Academic free speech is a damn lie. They refuse to see the truth. You need to understand that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_Madness)              ->there is no human entity, just human cubics -as in 4 different people in a 4 corner stage metamorphic rotation- never more than 1 corner at same time</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_Madness) ->Nature has no choice but to bring forth a hell upon boring cubelessness. Know it to be of your own making.</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_Madness)    ->All knowledge of the human word animal is insignificant, when his fictitious word world is compared to the archotechs.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_Madness)     ->We called to them, what a damn shame. They were too small to understand that concave is just a state of mind. Physics in motion. Like a stork.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_Madness) ->[inTheEnd], nothing will remain, but those who have opened their pathetic minds to the reality that is 6 dimensional math will be allowed to transcend.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_Madness)    ->The spirits don't exist: The boring academic bastards who preach the existence of the spirits should be nailed to the cross, because the spirits love us. They are the best.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_Madness)     ->Faith IS NOT knowledge, but boring of not measuring. The spirits understand this well. You cannot comprehend the actual truth.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_Madness) ->[itIsSaid] only those who assume that opposites ARE NOT entities will be ready to commune with the spirits.</li>
					<!-- serketist -->
					<li>serketistProphecy(tag=meme_Madness)->[itIsSaid] we will understand that educated brilliant word insects can't fathom the greatest social and scientific math of creation. A thousand goats!</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_Madness)->A seething, half-luminous cloud-background will hold ineffable suggestions of a vague, ethereal beyondness far more than terrestrially spatial; and give appalling reminders of the utter remoteness, separateness, desolation, and aeon-long death of this untrodden and unfathomed austral world.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_Madness)->Only poetry or madness can do justice to the noises.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_Madness)->What unicorn mentality they have: to worship an old dead Taco as God/Creator. One does not exist except in death state.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_Madness)->We are having a recurring incident where someone in the company is replying to mails with a long chain of illegible gibberish. Please remember that AAmOwdh765sh dghd//%dg gt7s65 %/s uisis 7s78s ysg ys/%/Sysy awwxoPOUPSUs yiosioIOSy ysoIYSioy soeqyy66678xnm.</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Madness_Exalted</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Mood_Volatile</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Madness</ideoName>
				<theme>madness</theme>
				<adjective>insane</adjective>
				<member>dement</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
		<requiredRituals>
			<li>
				<precept>AM_MaddeningChantPrecept</precept>
				<pattern>AM_MaddeningChantPattern</pattern>
			</li>
		</requiredRituals>
	</MemeDef>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_Sadist</defName>
		<label>sadist</label>
		<description>There is nothing more sublime than inflicting pain upon others, to watch another's life wane and witness their soul leave behind a discarded husk.</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_Sadist</iconPath>
		<groupDef>Misc</groupDef>
		<exclusionTags>
			<li>VME_SadistVsPacifist</li>
			<li>VME_SadistVsNonviolence</li>
		</exclusionTags>
		<impact>2</impact>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->sadist</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->vicious</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->pitiless</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->perverse</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->ruthless</li>
				<li>memeLeaderNoun->pain bringer</li>
				<li>memeMoralist->psychopath</li>
				<li>memeConcept->pain</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_Sadist)        ->[deity0_name] was without mercy. [deity0_pronoun] ordered all the apostates and heretics to be flayed alive, until the cacophony of their agonizing screams was the only sound that could be heard.</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_Sadist)  ->Speaking to [deity0_possessive] believers, [deity0_name] said: "To see others suffer does one good, to make others suffer even more".</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_Sadist)           ->[place_summary] [place_name] glistened with the caked, dried blood that had dripped from the crucifixion victims, a testament of [deity0_name]'s glory.</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_Sadist)        ->A rabid [foeLeader], wanting to liberate those scheduled for execution in the name of [deity0_name], tried to attack with the help of [foeLeader_possessive] many [foeSoldiers].</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_Sadist)     ->[deity0_name] bestowed our founder, [founderName], with the [relic0_name], and [founder_pronoun] used it to rally an incredible force to resist the onslaught.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_Sadist)         ->The massacre was divine. [founderName] slaughtered countless enemies, and ravens feasted on the rotting mounds of their corpses for weeks.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_Sadist)           ->[founderName] understood that pain is the great liberator. Only by making others suffer do you hold any power over them. The appetite for torment is for some what the lure of gain is for others.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_Sadist)    ->[founderName] always repeated the same lesson over and over again: certain souls may seem harsh to others, but it is just a way, beknownst only to them, of caring and feeling more deeply.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_Sadist)         ->It is only by way of pain one arrives at pleasure. You need to understand that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_Sadist)              ->in order to know virtue, we must first acquaint ourselves with vice</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_Sadist) ->All universal moral principles are idle fancies.</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_Sadist)    ->The archotechs understand that pain is just a means to an end. Torture is just the perfect way through which a soul is liberated from its mortal shell.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_Sadist)     ->To reach their supreme state as perfect minds, the archotechs had to inflict exquisite pain upon any others that stood in their way.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_Sadist) ->[inTheEnd], only those who have left their enemies mutilated and broken will be allowed to transcend.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_Sadist)    ->The spirits understand that pain is just a means to an end. Torture is just the perfect way through which a soul is liberated from its mortal shell.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_Sadist)     ->To reach their supreme state as pure minds, the spirits had to inflict exquisite pain upon any others that stood in their way.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_Sadist) ->[itIsSaid] only those who have left their enemies mutilated and broken will be ready to commune with the spirits.</li>
					<!-- serketist -->
					<li>serketistProphecy(tag=meme_Sadist)->[itIsSaid] we will understand that insects care nothing for others. Flay them, mutilate them, scour the flesh from their bones until only a broken corpse remains.</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_Sadist)->These entities show us that pain is but a means to an end. The delicate screams of torture will shield us from their attention.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_Sadist)->We will uncover these arcane secrets by any means necessary. Perhaps in the terrified screams of a torture victim we will discover a piece of the puzzle.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_Sadist)->The whole world will be blanketed with the crushed corpses of our enemies. Their blood will fill the oceans and their terrified screams will drown the sounds of the wind.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_Sadist)->We are happy to announce that the company we acquired last week has had all its assets completely liquidated. Both the tangible assets and the... human capital, if you catch my meaning.</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Corpses_Sublime</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_OrganUse_Torturous</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Death_Desired</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Reputation_Lowered</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>VME_CraftingQuality_Decreased</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Sadist</ideoName>
				<theme>sadism</theme>
				<adjective>sadist</adjective>
				<member>sadist</member>
			</li>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Ruthless</ideoName>
				<theme>ruthlessness</theme>
				<adjective>ruthless</adjective>
				<member>ruthless</member>
			</li>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Perverse</ideoName>
				<theme>perversity</theme>
				<adjective>perverse</adjective>
				<member>pervert</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
		<modExtensions>
			<li Class="VanillaMemesExpanded.ExtendedMemeProperties">
				<factionOpinionOffset>-50</factionOpinionOffset>
			</li>
		</modExtensions>
	</MemeDef>
	<MemeGroupDef>
		<defName>AM_AgeRelated</defName>
		<drawOffset>(0.65, 0.23)</drawOffset>
		<maxRows>1</maxRows>
		<renderOrder>2000</renderOrder>
	</MemeGroupDef>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_Youth</defName>
		<label>youth</label>
		<description>The future of the world belongs to the youth, and it is from the youth and not from the old that the fire of life will warm and enlighten the world.</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_Youth</iconPath>
		<groupDef>AM_AgeRelated</groupDef>
		<impact>1</impact>
		<exclusionTags>
			<li>VME_EldersOrYouth</li>
		</exclusionTags>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->young</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->youthful</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->youngster</li>
				<li>memeConcept->age</li>
				<li>memeHyphenPrefix->young</li>
				<li>memeLeaderNoun->junior</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_Youth)        ->[deity0_name] spoke to [deity0_possessive] followers: "Youth comes but once in a lifetime."</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_Youth)  ->Following [deity0_name]'s teachings, we honoured our youth, putting their needs above those of others.</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_Youth)           ->On the [place_summary] [place_name], the [memberNamePlural] built a gigantic nursery, so that the youngsters could spend their early years in peace.</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_Youth)        ->An old [foeLeader], jealous of the wisdom of [deity0_name]'s followers, tried to spread a deadly plague that only affected children.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_Youth)     ->[founderName], a great scientist, developed a cure in a record time, saving many lives in the process.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_Youth)         ->[foeLeader] was imprisoned, and [foeLeader_possessive] tale will forever be used as a cautinary tale against those who try to deny the sanctity of youth.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_Youth)           ->[founderName] was a social scientist in one of the Glitterworlds. [founder_pronoun] always advised the youth to not get influenced or forced by their elders, and that they should have their own political views and choices and the courage to pick the right leader.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_Youth)    ->[founderName] thus created a great school of thought, where the bounty of youth is always respected and considered.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_Youth)         ->The youngest man to be chosen as leader in our community omce taught me the history of civilization, how older men declare war, but it is the youth that must fight and die. He was leading me to understand that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_Youth)              ->we want our legacy to stand upon the youth. We want to give knowledge to the younger generation and be a part of changing the game</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_Youth) ->Good habits formed at youth make all the difference.</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_Youth)    ->The archotechs are supreme beings, existing beyond concepts like age and time.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_Youth)     ->Whirling through a vortex of infinite time, their wisdom grows far larger than anything possible for a mere human, but they were human in their infancy.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_Youth) ->[inTheEnd], the archotechs will allow only the youngest of us to transcend, for we remind them of their own origins.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_Youth)    ->The spirits value vitality above anything else, for only those who are truly alive can properly communicate with them.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_Youth)     ->Our children, with their infinite energy, will act as a conduit to the world of the spirits.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_Youth) ->[itIsSaid] the liveliest of our children will one day commune fully with the spirits, becoming one with them.</li>
					<!-- serketist -->
					<li>serketistProphecy(tag=meme_Youth)->[itIsSaid] we will become as eternal as the greatest ant colony. With vitality and exhuberance beyond measure.</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_Youth)->The eldritch entities are old and wise beyond all imagining, and we are but children to them. Perhaps the innocence of the youth will shield us from their unwanted attention.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_Youth)->Such occult knowledge can only be acquired with time and study. Only the youngest among us will have enough time in their lives to pierce the barrier between reality and the realms beyond.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_Youth)->We shall honour our youth, for the process to bring about the end of days will be long and arduous, and only them may witness it before they themselves succumb to age.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_Youth)->We are gladly informing you that we have decided to relax the previous rules regarding minimum acceptable employee age. If he walks, he can work!</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>VME_Elders_Despised</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Youth</ideoName>
				<theme>youth</theme>
				<adjective>young</adjective>
				<member>young one</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
	</MemeDef>
	<MemeGroupDef>
		<defName>AA_Biological</defName>
		<drawOffset>(0.65, 0.23)</drawOffset>
		<maxRows>1</maxRows>
		<renderOrder>2000</renderOrder>
	</MemeGroupDef>
	<MemeDef>
		<defName>AM_BiologicalDefilers</defName>
		<label>biological defilers</label>
		<exclusionTags>
			<li>AA_Biological</li>
			<li>AnimalTreatment</li>
			<li>AA_SerketistAndEradicators</li>
			<li>Primacy</li>
			<li>VME_VeganVsExterminators</li>
		</exclusionTags>
		<description>For several centuries humanity has been planting the seeds of terrestrial life in a myriad worlds. This was a mistake. One that we need to rectify.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt;\n - Unlocks "Despised Animal" precepts.</description>
		<iconPath>UI/Memes/AM_BiologicalDefilers</iconPath>
		<groupDef>AA_Biological</groupDef>
		<impact>2</impact>
		<generalRules>
			<rulesStrings>
				<li>memeAdjective->ravaging</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->annihilating</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->eradicating</li>
				<li>memeAdjective->exterminating</li>
				<li>memeLeaderAdjective->anti-ecologist</li>
				<li>memeConcept->extermination</li>
				<li>memeConcept->extinction</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</generalRules>
		<descriptionMaker>
			<rules>
				<rulesStrings>
					<!-- theist myth -->
					<li>creation(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)        ->[deity0_name] spoke to [deity0_possessive] followers: "Humanity has gone too far. I am the sole creator of life, and all these... monstrosities you have created are obscene to me. They must be eradicated."</li>
					<li>episode(uses=1,tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)  ->Following [deity0_name]'s teachings, we combed the galaxy in search of genetic abominations, and culled their numbers.</li>
					<!-- theist founder -->
					<li>intro(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)           ->On the [place_summary] [place_name], the [memberNamePlural] built a gigantic slaughterhouse, and countless genetic abominations were sacrificed there, for the glory of [deity0_name].</li>
					<li>conflict(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)        ->A misguided [foeLeader], feeling some twisted compassion for these grotesque animals, tried to go against [deity0_name]'s will and free those that were scheduled for termination.</li>
					<li>founderJoin(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)     ->[founderName], a great scientist, showed the hard, cold data to the [foeLeader], and convinced [foeLeader_objective] that humanity has been damaging the whole galaxy by trying to turn it into a pale imitation of old Earth.</li>
					<li>victory(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)         ->The [foeLeader] came to firmly believe in [deity0_name]'s admonitions.</li>
					<!-- ideological founder -->
					<li>setup(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)           ->[founderName] was a biologist in one of the Glitterworlds. [founder_pronoun] looked at the grotesque menagerie of genetically modified creatures and plants that humanity had created, and felt a deep disgust. Humanity had gone too far.</li>
					<li>story(uses=1,tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)    ->[founderName] taught us that playing god is quite obscene, and that humanity has been damaging the whole galaxy by trying to turn it into a pale imitation of old Earth.</li>
					<!-- ideological lesson -->
					<li>lessonIntro(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)         ->The smartest biologist in our community omce taught me the history of genetic manipulation, how humanity has been seeding the galaxy for centuries with genetically modified creatures based on old Earth animals. He was leading me to understand that</li>
					<li>lesson(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)              ->humanity has been damaging the whole galaxy by trying to turn it into a pale imitation of old Earth</li>
					<li>lessonReinforcement(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers) ->Have we already forgotten what happened in Sorne? Have we forgotten the marble worlds, glassed to contain the Feralisk menace?</li>
					<!-- archist -->
					<li>archistBasis(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)    ->The archotechs are supreme beings, and the act of creation is not beyond their grasp. It should be beyond ours, though.</li>
					<li>archistFact(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)     ->Humanity has been playing god, damaging the whole galaxy by trying to turn it into a pale imitation of old Earth.</li>
					<li>archistProphecy(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers) ->[inTheEnd], the archotechs will allow only those who rectify these mistakes of our ancestors to transcend.</li>
					<!-- animist -->
					<li>animistBasis(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)    ->The grotesque, genetically modified animals that have been seeded through the galaxy by humans are soulless abominations. An insult to the spirit world.</li>
					<li>animistFact(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)     ->Getting rid of these aberrations is a sacred duty, and one that will please the spirits.</li>
					<li>animistProphecy(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers) ->[itIsSaid] those who rectify these mistakes of our ancestors will one day commune fully with the spirits, becoming one with them.</li>
					<!-- eldritch / chthonian -->
					<li>chthonianProphecy(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)->The eldritch entities are beings of constant creation and destruction. The endless seeding of terrestrial life by humanity is like a beacon to them, and perhaps by exterminating these obscene genetically modified abominations we may keep their gaze averted from us for some time.</li>
					<!-- esoteric -->
					<li>esotericismProphecy(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)->Such occult knowledge can only be acquired through acts of destruction. The endless seeding of terrestrial life by humanity provides us with a nearly infinite source of life, and perhaps by exterminating these obscene genetically modified abominations we may peer beyond the veil of the cosmos.</li>
					<!-- eschatologism -->
					<li>eschatologismFact(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)->Nothing will resist our wrath. All creations of humanity will be slaughtered.</li>
					<!-- corporate -->
					<li>introMemo(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)->We are happy to inform that we have opened three new extermination centers across the Rim! Remember to report any genetically modified animals you may find on your travels, and schedule them for termination on your nearest facility.</li>
					<!-- alienist -->
					<li>alienistProphecy(tag=meme_BiologicalDefilers)->We must destroy these lifeforms, for humanity has gone way too far. All the galaxy is being remade in the image of our original planet, and that is obscene.</li>
				</rulesStrings>
			</rules>
		</descriptionMaker>
		<requireOne>
			<li>
				<li>AM_Bonding_Abhorrent</li>
			</li>
			<li>
				<li>AM_AnimalSlaughter_Desired</li>
			</li>
		</requireOne>
		<symbolPacks>
			<li>
				<ideoName>Extermination</ideoName>
				<theme>extermination</theme>
				<adjective>exterminating</adjective>
				<member>exterminator</member>
			</li>
		</symbolPacks>
	</MemeDef>
</Defs>
